musicfever.org 2003-12-05

# PRIVACY STATEMENT

**PRIVACY STATEMENT**

**_Information Collection and Use_ __**

**Information Collection**

Music Fever is the sole owner of the information collected on Music Fever. Music Fever collects information from our member and visitor at several different points on our Web site.

Service of Music Fever is free, visitor will not require to signup to use our service. Visitor can signup our membership service and during the registration process, personal information are require to submit. Other information such as visitors' internet protocol (IP) will collected by Music Fever's site tracker.

Visitor who become member of Music Fever will need to submit personal information for registration process. For more information about membership service please go to our Membership Privacy page. 

**Information Use **

Music Fever will gather information through cookies, log files, and/or third parties as a reference information to improve and advance our site. Music Fever will also collect information from the people who applying membership of Music Fever.  For more information about membership service please go to our Membership Privacy page. 

Music Fever will not distributes any information that collected in through our mailing list to third party.

### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the visitor’s computer tied to information about the visitor.  Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site.  We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies.  For the session ID cookie, once visitors close the browser, the cookie simply terminates.  A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the visitor’s hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. <http://www.cookiecentral.com/>

Music Fever only use cookie in tracking. The use of persistent cookies in our site is to enable us to track and target the interests of our visitors to enhance the experience on our site. 

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers).  However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. 

### Third Party Advertising

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to visitors by Focus IN, our Web advertising partner. Information about visitors’ visit to this site, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not visitor name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to visitors on this site. For more information about Focus IN, cookies, and how to "opt-out", please [click here](http://www.focusin.com/).

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Music Fever only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

### Log Files

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files.  This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track visitor’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.  IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We use a tracking utility called [Webalizer](http://www.mrunix.net/webalizer/) that uses log files to analyze visitor movement.

**Communications from the Site **

## Customer Service

We communicate with visitors on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to song request we reply via email, in accordance with the visitors wishes.

Membership

Please go to our Membership Privacy page for information. 

**Sharing **

## Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve visitor privacy, we may need to disclose visitors'  information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

## Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)

We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers.  Music Fever has place Focus IN's advertising banner code in our webpage for the purpose of advertisement. The banner code is able to capture aggregate information such as Internet protocol (IP), language, operating system, Internet browser of the visitor's computer that is using and also the number of visit of that visitor.  This is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

## Third Party Advertisers

Music Fever shares Web site usage information about visitors with a reputable third party Focus IN for the purpose of targeting our Internet banner advertisements on this site and other sites.  For example, Music Fever uses cookies on this site for the purpose of site tracking. The information they collect and share through this technology is not personally identifiable.  For more information about our third-party advertiser or for choices about not having this anonymous information used please [click here](http://www.focusin.com/).

**These are the instances in which we will share visitors’ personal information:**

We DO NOT Share Personal Information with Third Parties. we gather visitor's aggregate information (refer to Aggregate Information section above for more information about aggregate information) other than that, we also collect visitors' name, email address, and ICQ number for notification purpose.

## Links

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Music Fever, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.  We encourage our visitor to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.  This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

## Chat Rooms, Message Boards, and Public Forums

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online \- for example on message boards, through e-mail, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, by posting personal information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

##  

## Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our visitors are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

If, however, we are going to use visitors’ personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify visitors by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days.

## Contact Information

If visitor have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: [MessageBox](http://www.musicfever.org/messagebox/)

<http://www.musicfever.org/>
